So AIPAC is just a source of funding to accomplish the the goals of the ruling class, a specific group of ruling class to extend the influence of the U.S. empire.
There are different interests that the ruling class has, but what often wins out is who is able to front that money.
And that is where AIPAC comes in, in being able to fund politicians to pass the agenda of a particular section of the U.S. empire's ruling class.
Which focuses primarily in West Asia.
So it's like money laundering.
Basically. Yeah. I mean, because we we give money to Israel, like billions of dollars a year.
And then they give it back back through Super PAC, AIPAC.
And so it's just basically like recycling the money that is given to them after they've taken their money laundering our taxpayer dollars.
That's what they're doing. Exactly. And they take a cut of it by purchasing weapons, providing free health care.
Providing free education in Israel. And the rest comes back to continue that cycle.
You see, this is why I like having you on the goddamn show.